Once upon a time, there was a young man with a beautiful face.
The people loved the handsome young man,
but he never showed the slightest interest in loving anyone.
This was because all he loved was himself.
When the young man who neglected to love and sought only to be loved
found someone for whom he truly cared,
he realized that he had lost even the words to express those feelings.
To be continued...
To be...
to be...
To be continued...
To be...
to be...
Do you think it's possible to turn a love that's been made impure back to normal?
Right now, I want you to stick to Mewto as close as you can, so that way...
A wandering knight unable to do anything?
I think the role fits you to a tee, Fakir.
Maybe he's preparing a place for me to die.
Your sword is seeking blood, isn't it?
Cut down that useless excuse for a knight!
Stop! Please, Fakir, do not fight!
All you children who love stories, come gather round!
See you below.